marketersmedia.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy « MarketersMEDIA – Press Release Distribution Services – News Release Distribution Services

MarketersMedia.com is a newswire service which distributes press releases on behalf of our customers. Your privacy is very important to us. We are committed to establishing and maintaining policies and procedures which protect the privacy of personal information gathered from our customers and visitors from our website. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

 **Information Gathered from Visitors**

When visiting MarketersMedia.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is only used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, ALL recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website. They may be used to track your return visits to the website.

Where registration is required, the visitor’s email, username and other relevant information will be stored on the server. Email addresses will NEVER be sold, rented or leased to 3rd parties. Emails may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers by us.

 **Third-Party Sites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

From time to time, the contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. To keep up-to-date with MarketersMedia.com policy, please check this page periodically. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of MarketersMedia.com, you may contact us at MarketersMedia [at] danieltan.zendesk.com

The information we collect is disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at MarketersMedia [at] danieltan.zendesk.com
